[Music]
experts love Singapore for many things
superior healthcare is one but it does
get more expensive every year which is
why a corporate medical plan may not be
enough and sometimes it doesn't cover
everyone at home what if all of you can
be protected in Singapore and overseas
FWD international health insurance gives
you a comprehensive plan that stays with
you wherever you go whether you're
traveling for work leisure or a trip
home you get access to medical
facilities around the world with our
cashless facilities if needed we also
cover emergency medical evacuation and
repatriation there's more when you stay
healthy and keep out of the hospital
you'll see your coverage double under
our plan and if you've exhausted your
annual limit we're still here for you
your coverage will be reloaded
automatically which can be used if an
accident puts you in the hospital
getting after the UD international
health insurance is easy do it yourself
online pick the add-ons that you need
and within minutes you'll be covered by
your personalized plan get your quote
online now and get covered for up to
three million dollars a year
[Music]